healthines.com 2014-12-19

# healthines.com » Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how healthines.com uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.  
healthines.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
healthines.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from September 2010.  
What we collect  
We may collect the following information:  
Name  
Contact information including email address  
Demographic information such as zipcode, preferences and interests  
Other information relevant to your participation a course, tour or event in the case of online class and event  
registration  
What we do with the information we gather  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service, and in particular for the  
following reasons:  
Internal record keeping.  
We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
If you do not exclude yourself, we may periodically send promotional email about new services, special events or  
other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
We may use the information to help connect you with the most appropriate department, unit or individual based on your request.  
We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.  
We will never sell your information.  
Security  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure  
we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information  
we collect online.  
How we use cookies  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file  
is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow  
web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs,  
likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic  
and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical  
analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than  
the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.  
Links to other websites  
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.  
Controlling your personal information  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do  
not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.  
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at webmaster@healthines.com.  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.
